A lot of times you'll be working with projects that require
很多时候 你要处理的项目需要
different library versions or different versions of python even.
不同的库版本 甚至不同版本的 python
In my experience and in many other people's' it's really difficult to get
根据我的经验和许多其他人的经验 这真的很难得到
all these versions to play nicely together on one computer.
所有这些版本在同一台电脑上可以很好的配合
To solve this problem we use virtual environments managed with libraries such
为了解决这个问题 我们使用虚拟环境管理的库 如
as Virtualenv.
作为 Virtualenv
Virtual environments let you separate libraries required by
使用虚拟环境可以将
different projects, so you can avoid conflicts.
不同的项目 这样你就可以避免冲突
If you're working with data though, Anaconda is the way to go.
如果你正在处理数据 那么蟒蛇就是你的选择
Anaconda is a distribution of libraries and software specifically built for
Anaconda 是一个图书馆和软件的分发专门为
data science.
数据科学
It comes with Conda, a package and
它带有康达 一个包裹和
environment manager that will make your life a thousand times better.
环境管理员 将使你的生活一千倍更好
Now I'll show you a bit about using Conda.
现在我将向你们展示一些使用 Conda 的方法
I generally create a new environment for each project I start,
我通常会为我开始的每个项目创建一个新的环境,
this way I can keep the necessary package versions separate.
这样我就可以将必要的包版本分离开来
For example if I want to start a new project using Python 3.
例如 如果我想使用 python3启动一个新项目
Which you should be using for all new projects,
你应该在所有的新项目中使用它,
I can create an environment for it.
我可以为它创造一个环境
Type in conde create, give it a name, tea_facts.
输入 conde create 给它一个名字 tea _ facts
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[ BLANK _ audio ]
It's a bot that tweets facts about tea and
这是一个发布关于茶的事实的机器人
the python version, three and enter.
Python 版本 三 然后进入
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[ BLANK _ audio ]
This will create the environment for me.
这将为我创造环境
Now, I can enter the environment like so, source activate tea_facts.
现在 我可以像这样进入环境 源激活茶事实
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[ BLANK _ audio ]
This is the command on Mac in Linux, on Window it's just activate.
这是 Linux 系统中 Mac 上的命令 在 windows 上它只是被激活
Now I'm in the environment, you can see the name in the prompt.
现在我在环境中 您可以在提示符中看到名称
And you can see here the packages that are installed,
你们可以看到这里安装的软件包,
these are just the default packages.
这些只是默认的包裹
Now I can start installing what I want for this projects.
现在我可以开始为这个项目安装我想要的东西了
Let's install Numpy Pandas, for working with the t data and matplotlib for
让我们安装 numpypandas 用于处理 t 数据和 matplotlib
making visualization.
形象化
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[ BLANK _ audio ]
Then I'll start notebooks which I like to use to develop code.
然后我会开始使用笔记本电脑来开发代码
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[ BLANK _ audio ]
And again looking at the installed packages.
再次查看已安装的软件包
I have all these ready to use for my project.
我有所有这些准备使用我的项目
And these are separated from other environments, so
这些是与其他环境分开的 所以
I won't run into any conflicting version issues.
我不会遇到任何版本冲突的问题
Okay, now it's your turn to learn how to use Conda for your own projects,
好了现在轮到你学习如何在自己的项目中使用 Conda 了,
because that thing will take around 30 minutes up to an hour.
因为那东西要花30分钟到1小时
Okay, have fun.
好的 玩得开心 .最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6